[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "What is the real strategy at this stage of the battle plan that you think he needs to be most aware of?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "real", "strategy", "at", "this", "stage", "of", "the", "battle", "plan", "that", "you", "think", "he", "needs", "to", "be", "most", "aware", "of", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "I think it's very obvious, Piers, and that's jobs and the economy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "very", "obvious", ",", "Piers", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "jobs", "and", "the", "economy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary Clinton", "Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", ",", "``", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 58, "question": "How much of a problem is it going to be if Barack Obama begins replaying that criticism and indeed from other senior Republicans to say, come on, even you guys didn't think he was that great?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "a", "problem", "is", "it", "going", "to", "be", "if", "Barack", "Obama", "begins", "replaying", "that", "criticism", "and", "indeed", "from", "other", "senior", "Republicans", "to", "say", ",", "come", "on", ",", "even", "you", "guys", "did", "n't", "think", "he", "was", "that", "great", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "Well, probably the same impression that people have when they show Hillary Clinton saying, \"Shame on you, Barack Obama.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "probably", "the", "same", "impression", "that", "people", "have", "when", "they", "show", "Hillary", "Clinton", "saying", ",", "``", "Shame", "on", "you", ",", "Barack", "Obama", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Or as some other people say, look, it's fine, he did create jobs, but he also wrecked a lot of jobs?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "as", "some", "other", "people", "say", ",", "look", ",", "it", "'s", "fine", ",", "he", "did", "create", "jobs", ",", "but", "he", "also", "wrecked", "a", "lot", "of", "jobs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "You know, the problem with the free enterprise system is that not everybody succeeds.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "the", "problem", "with", "the", "free", "enterprise", "system", "is", "that", "not", "everybody", "succeeds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 104, "question": "Why doesn't he just do it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "does", "n't", "he", "just", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 105, "answer": "Well, first of all, let me put this in context.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "let", "me", "put", "this", "in", "context", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "But just to clarify, you never saw anything that you think would cause him embarrassment?", "question_tokens": ["But", "just", "to", "clarify", ",", "you", "never", "saw", "anything", "that", "you", "think", "would", "cause", "him", "embarrassment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Of course not.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chicago"]}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "What does Chicago-style mean?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "Chicago-style", "mean", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Chicago style means that there's very few depths you won't plummet.", "answer_tokens": ["Chicago", "style", "means", "that", "there", "'s", "very", "few", "depths", "you", "wo", "n't", "plummet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "Seriously, the lowest you've ever seen?", "question_tokens": ["Seriously", ",", "the", "lowest", "you", "'ve", "ever", "seen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "I have not seen anyone accused of possibly being a felon.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "not", "seen", "anyone", "accused", "of", "possibly", "being", "a", "felon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "I'm not sure you can do that kind of campaign and then honestly stand back and go, come on, you're not being fair to me, can you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "you", "can", "do", "that", "kind", "of", "campaign", "and", "then", "honestly", "stand", "back", "and", "go", ",", "come", "on", ",", "you", "'re", "not", "being", "fair", "to", "me", ",", "can", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "VB", ",", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "Well, your point is well made in this respect.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "your", "point", "is", "well", "made", "in", "this", "respect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "What should be done about this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "should", "be", "done", "about", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "What we should have done a long time ago was join with other nations and set up a safe zone and together provide arms and equipment to the resistance fighters who are being massacred.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "we", "should", "have", "done", "a", "long", "time", "ago", "was", "join", "with", "other", "nations", "and", "set", "up", "a", "safe", "zone", "and", "together", "provide", "arms", "and", "equipment", "to", "the", "resistance", "fighters", "who", "are", "being", "massacred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "Is it time that President Obama did something?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "time", "that", "President", "Obama", "did", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "Yes, and one of the sad aspects of this, he doesn't even speak up on these people's behalf.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "one", "of", "the", "sad", "aspects", "of", "this", ",", "he", "does", "n't", "even", "speak", "up", "on", "these", "people", "'s", "behalf", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 208, "question": "And you've met some of these people?", "question_tokens": ["And", "you", "'ve", "met", "some", "of", "these", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 209, "answer": "I've met them in a refugee camps.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'ve", "met", "them", "in", "a", "refugee", "camps", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "What do you say to that charge?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "charge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "I say that's true but I also think that there's a variety of reasons, including a polarization amongst the American people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "that", "'s", "true", "but", "I", "also", "think", "that", "there", "'s", "a", "variety", "of", "reasons", ",", "including", "a", "polarization", "amongst", "the", "American", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I think that it's a very unique interpretation of the real world to say that money is speech.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "unique", "interpretation", "of", "the", "real", "world", "to", "say", "that", "money", "is", "speech", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "What is the fundamental principle issue here that you object to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "fundamental", "principle", "issue", "here", "that", "you", "object", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "The fundamental principle is that it bring -- it does not rein in any way the activities of the labor unions.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "fundamental", "principle", "is", "that", "it", "bring", "--", "it", "does", "not", "rein", "in", "any", "way", "the", "activities", "of", "the", "labor", "unions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "You would sign up for that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "sign", "up", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "How do you feel when people say, we've got the real John McCain?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "people", "say", ",", "we", "'ve", "got", "the", "real", "John", "McCain", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "I say I never left.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "say", "I", "never", "left", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John McCain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 332, "question": "Would you like Michele Bachmann to apologize?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "like", "Michele", "Bachmann", "to", "apologize", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "I don't know --", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "-- in particular?", "question_tokens": ["--", "in", "particular", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "I don't know what she should do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "she", "should", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Maricopa County", "United States of America"]}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "What does it say about the state of modern politics, that that kind of thing can happen?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "say", "about", "the", "state", "of", "modern", "politics", ",", "that", "that", "kind", "of", "thing", "can", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Listen, we just had a sheriff of Maricopa County, again, who has taken it upon himself to prove that President Obama was not born in the United States of America.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "we", "just", "had", "a", "sheriff", "of", "Maricopa", "County", ",", "again", ",", "who", "has", "taken", "it", "upon", "himself", "to", "prove", "that", "President", "Obama", "was", "not", "born", "in", "the", "United", "States", "of", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Well, I think you need to say one thing more, which is what does it tell you about the state of politics?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "you", "need", "to", "say", "one", "thing", "more", ",", "which", "is", "what", "does", "it", "tell", "you", "about", "the", "state", "of", "politics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CD", "NN", "JJR", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "It's crazy.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "crazy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "What goes through the mind of a wife in this situation?", "question_tokens": ["What", "goes", "through", "the", "mind", "of", "a", "wife", "in", "this", "situation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "It is day by day.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "day", "by", "day", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Was that your memory of it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "that", "your", "memory", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "Yeah, its exhilarating.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "its", "exhilarating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "Do you actually regret -- if you're honest, do you look in the mirror and regret at least going for it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "actually", "regret", "--", "if", "you", "'re", "honest", ",", "do", "you", "look", "in", "the", "mirror", "and", "regret", "at", "least", "going", "for", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "Oh, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "CC", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "It could have worked?", "question_tokens": ["It", "could", "have", "worked", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "CCAIN: Well, it's not that it could or couldn't have.", "answer_tokens": ["CCAIN", ":", "Well", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "that", "it", "could", "or", "could", "n't", "have", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "When you were in Vietnam, and you went through five, six years of absolute hell, repeated tortures, beatings, so on, what did you learn about yourself that has now dictated the way you are as a politician?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "in", "Vietnam", ",", "and", "you", "went", "through", "five", ",", "six", "years", "of", "absolute", "hell", ",", "repeated", "tortures", ",", "beatings", ",", "so", "on", ",", "what", "did", "you", "learn", "about", "yourself", "that", "has", "now", "dictated", "the", "way", "you", "are", "as", "a", "politician", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "I was proud of my ability to resist all kinds of pressures from my captors, both mental and physical.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "proud", "of", "my", "ability", "to", "resist", "all", "kinds", "of", "pressures", "from", "my", "captors", ",", "both", "mental", "and", "physical", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vietnam"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "If I could relive -- outside marriage and children, if I could have the power to let you relieve five minutes of your live, what would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "relive", "--", "outside", "marriage", "and", "children", ",", "if", "I", "could", "have", "the", "power", "to", "let", "you", "relieve", "five", "minutes", "of", "your", "live", ",", "what", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ":", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "Probably the day I left prison.", "answer_tokens": ["Probably", "the", "day", "I", "left", "prison", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Do you agree with him?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "agree", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Yes, I don't disagree with him at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "disagree", "with", "him", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "I mean, do they have a point?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "do", "they", "have", "a", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "I don't think we know enough about the opposition yet.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "know", "enough", "about", "the", "opposition", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "When would the military possibly turn on Assad?", "question_tokens": ["When", "would", "the", "military", "possibly", "turn", "on", "Assad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "JJ", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "Yeah, that's an interesting point.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "that", "'s", "an", "interesting", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 499, "question": "And what should be done about it?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "should", "be", "done", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 500, "answer": "I saw that attack as an indicator of what I see as the era that we're in.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "saw", "that", "attack", "as", "an", "indicator", "of", "what", "I", "see", "as", "the", "era", "that", "we", "'re", "in", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "Did you feel optimism there?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "feel", "optimism", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120719pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "Why is this happening and what can be done about it?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "this", "happening", "and", "what", "can", "be", "done", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "This is an issue that we in the military have been working very hard for years.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "an", "issue", "that", "we", "in", "the", "military", "have", "been", "working", "very", "hard", "for", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]